<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>SudoDoas Blog</title>
<link>sudodoas.github.io</link>
<description>The best blog on the block</description>



<item>
<title>Website builder vs HTML</title>
<link>https://sudodoas.github.io/blog/articles/builderVsHtml.html</link>
<guid>https://sudodoas.github.io/blog/articles/builderVsHtml.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sun 6 Sep 2020</pubDate>
<description>A brief comparison between website builders and HTML</description>
		<p>
		There are two main options to choose from when choosing how to build your website:
		<strong>HTML</strong> or <strong>website builder</strong>. The option you choose will affect the amount of time you site 
		takes to make and the amount of customizability that you have over your site.
		</p>
		<p>
        When building a website with HTML, one has to manually type out all of the elements that they will use in their site.
        This takes a lot of <strong>time</strong> which will be a hindrance if the site has a specific deadline. Website builders enable you to 
        launch a working website in a couple of hours or even less than an hour.
		</p>
		<p>
        Website builders allow you to drag and drop elements onto a template which will become your webpage. There are only a limited amount of
        features that you can use. If you want to use more features, you have to pay for them. Even with additional features, website builders
        don't allow you to do everything. With HTML, you have the <strong>freedom</strong> to use any of the avalible features in HTML and you are not limimted
        to the placement and styling of your elements.
		</p>
		<p>
        Another factor to take into account when choosing your method of building your website is the amount of <strong>learning</strong> that you will have 
        to do. Website builders like Wix and Google Sites are very intuitive. HTML is a language that has to be learned. You have to follow
        a specific syntax when using it.
		</p>
		<p>
        At the end of the day, you are free to choose which method you will use to make your website. Use this page as a guideline to help you 
        choose. My opinion is that everyone should learn HTML as it is a useful skill to learn.
		</p>
</item>



<item>
<title>My first blog</title>
<link>https://sudodoas.github.io/blog/articles/welcomes.html</link>
<guid>https://sudodoas.github.io/blog/articles/welcomes.html</guid>
<pubDate>Sat 5 Sep 2020</pubDate>
<description>Welcome to my new blog.</description>
<p>Welcome to my new blog. I do not currently know what I will be blogging about.
	I will try and start an RSS feed. Please feel free to e-mail me at <strong>libretiger@protonmail.com</strong>
	with any comments or concerns. I will try to base my blogs on educational content.
	Do not spam my e-mail and please be respectful
</p>
<p>
  "My only agenda is love, fam." - Matthew Bedser
</p>
</item>



</channel>
</rss>
